Melissa Ann Rice is a motivational speaker, mental health and anti-bullying advocate, and author of The People You Meet in Real Life. She is a 2009 honors graduate of Immaculata University and speaks with Minding Your Minds speaking program about mental health specifically Depression, Anxiety, Obsessive Compulsive Disorder, anti-bullying, positive coping and peer support and is on the board of the Philadelphia chapter of the American Foundation for Suicide Prevention (AFSP). She mentors a student run peer-to-peer support group called CogWell at the University of Pennsylvania and has been recognized for her advocacy work with numerous awards including the honorable mention Jerry Greenspan Student Voice of Mental Health Award given by the Jed Foundation of America at a gala in June 2009 in New York City.