<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Illumination</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Illumination</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tasklist_selector">tasklist_selector</string>
    <string-array name="videoNames">
        <item>Dog Video #1</item>
        <item>Dog Video #2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="inspirationalquotes">
        <item>When it is darkest, we can see the stars.     - Ralph Waldo Emerson</item>
        <item>Place your hand over your heart, can you feel it? That is called purpose. You’re alive for a reason so don’t ever give up.  - Unknown</item>
        <item>Never never never give up.    - Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>When the whole world is silent, even one voice becomes powerful. - Malala </item>
        <item>The world is a better place with you in it. - Unknown </item>
        <item>Feelings are just visitors. Let them come and go</item>
        <item>Your speed doesn’t matter. Forward is forward</item>
        <item>The real man smiles in trouble, gathers strength from distress, and grows brave by reflection.</item>
        <item>Brave men rejoice in adversity, just as brave soldiers triumph in war.</item>
        <item>Always seek out the seed of triumph in every adversity.</item>
        <item>Start by doing whats necessary; then do whats possible; and suddenly you are doing the impossible</item>
        <item>Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome. -Booker T. Washington</item>
        <item>Turn your wounds into wisdom -Oprah Winfrey</item>
        <item>I cant change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination. -Jimmy Dean</item>
        <item>I hated every minute of training, but I said, Dont quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion. -Muhammad Ali</item>
        <item>Your big opportunity may be right where you are now</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="activities_list">
        <item>Imagining you are walking through a meadow</item>
        <item>Discover the therapeutic value of working in the garden</item>
        <item>Volunteer for a good cause</item>
        <item>Use a tension-relief roller</item>
        <item>Decrease your workload</item>
        <item>Call and talk to a friend</item>
        <item>Get polarity therapy</item>
        <item>Do a random act of kindness</item>
        <item>Relish a favorite memory</item>
        <item>Step outside and savor the sunlight</item>
        <item>Take a nap</item>
        <item>Do progressive muscle relaxation, starting with the feet and moving toward the head</item>
        <item>Stretch for a few minutes</item>
        <item>List all the things you love about yourself</item>
        <item>Forgive yourself for the things you \"think\" you\'ve done wrong -- move on</item>
        <item>Put on your favorite outfit</item>
        <item>Spend time with family over a good meal</item>
        <item>Create handmade thank you notes</item>
        <item>Drink a cup of relaxation-inducing herbal tea, such as chamomile</item>
        <item>Look back through pictures of happy memories -- family vacations and special events -- and focus on how happy you were</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="activities_catagories">
        <item>Activities For You</item>
        <item>Volunteering</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="StoryTitles">
        <item>Meet Ali</item>
        <item>Meet Andrew</item>
        <item>Meet Melissa</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="faqlist">
        <item>What is Illumination</item>
        <item>About Neel</item>
        <item>About Srija</item>
        <item>About Trisha</item>
        <item>Future Works</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
